export const Questions = [
    {
      prompt: "Which of the following is not a Java feature?",
      optionA: "Object-Oriented",
      optionB: "Use of pointers",
      optionC: "Portable",
      optionD: "Dynamic",
      answer: "optionB",
    },
    {
      prompt: "What is the size of int variable?",
      optionA: "8 bit",
      optionB: "16 bit",
      optionC: "32 bit",
      optionD: "64 bit",
      answer: "optionC",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of these keywords is used to define interfaces in Java?",
      optionA: "intf",
      optionB: "Intf",
      optionC: "interface",
      optionD: "Interface",
      answer: "optionC",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of these cannot be used for a variable name in Java?",
      optionA: "identifier",
      optionB: "keyword",
      optionC: "identifier_1",
      optionD: "$identifier",
      answer: "optionB",
    },
    {
      prompt: "What is the default value of a boolean variable?",
      optionA: "true",
      optionB: "false",
      optionC: "null",
      optionD: "0",
      answer: "optionB",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of the following is a valid declaration of a char?",
      optionA: "char ch = '\\utea';",
      optionB: "char ca = 'tea';",
      optionC: "char cr = \u0223;",
      optionD: "char cc = '\\itea';",
      answer: "optionA",
    },
    {
      prompt: "What is the output of the following code?\n\n int a = 5; int b = 10; System.out.println(a + b);",
      optionA: "15",
      optionB: "510",
      optionC: "5 + 10",
      optionD: "Error",
      answer: "optionA",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of the following is true about inheritance in Java?",
      optionA: "Private methods are inherited",
      optionB: "Protected methods are inherited",
      optionC: "Static methods are inherited",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: "optionB",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which of these is not a valid constructor?",
      optionA: "MyClass()",
      optionB: "MyClass(int a)",
      optionC: "MyClass(int a, int b)",
      optionD: "MyClass MyClass()",
      answer: "optionD",
    },
    {
      prompt: "Which package contains the Random class?",
      optionA: "java.util package",
      optionB: "java.lang package",
      optionC: "java.io package",
      optionD: "java.net package",
      answer: "optionA",
    }
  ];
  